OKURA FILM
JAPAN-CHINA JOINT PRODUCTION
Produced by Okura Pictures Co., Ltd. Toho Film Company
Chinese Ghost Story: Breaking A Coffin
Okinawan Ghost Story: The Upside-Down Ghost
Producer
Mitsugu Okura
Written by Mitsuo Kaneda & Minoru Matsui
Composed by Toshiro Omi and Sadao Nagase
Sound Design - Toshio Takubo
Lighting - Yukio Ichikawa
Cinematography by Hidemitsu Iwahashi
Assistant Supervisor - Kinya Ogawa
Art by Kurosawa Yasayoshi and Xiao Paiming
Cast
Shinsuke Mikimoto
Joji Ohara
Kyoko Ogimachi
Tamaki Katori
Directed by Satoru Kobayashi and Shao Lo-Hui
Ну что, пойдем?
Осторожно
Хотелось бы еще посмотреть...
Что-то случилось?